Ending
Here we go... Upokami!
This time I'll be talking with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。
Emi Kasai of Chibaki Factory.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
our recordings and rehearsals.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with the behind-the-scenes of our two MCs.
I, Ishida...
We have decided to release the DVD of the birthday event in April.
I'd like to talk about it.
As soon as we announced that the DVD of the birthday event is going to be released
I'd like to announce that the DVD of the birthday event will be released, and at the same time, we'll post the announcement video on YouTube.
I've been telling my fans to watch it every year, but it's a little embarrassing for me to watch it.
but sometimes I'm too embarrassed to watch it myself.
But this year, I'd like to watch it.
But this year, I want to see it.
I had a lot of fun at the birthday event.
and I had a sense of fulfillment that I had done something worthwhile.
I decided to take a look.
I thought I'd take a look at it and see how happy I was.
I don't know if I would have recognized myself in the past.
I was a person who didn't give myself much credit.
Now I'm 27 years old.
I've become a person who can admit to myself that I'm working hard and having fun.
I was happy that I could feel myself growing as a human being there.
You are so cool!
Actually, I'm a little bit like you.
I'm a little embarrassed to see it.
But after hearing what you just said, I hope I can look at myself objectively.
I would like to talk about the dance lessons we took together after the new member joined the group.
After I joined the group, a new member joined the group and became the first senior member.
We took dance lessons together.
I think it was a good opportunity for me to reevaluate my own dance and to talk about the new member.
We talked about the new member.
I remember when I first joined the group.
I could go back to my original mind when I joined the group, or I could feel myself as a senior member.
I think I can be a good role model if I can improve my dance more and more.
I felt that I was able to look at things a little more objectively now.
I see, I think it's a wonderful change to have a new member.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's start with the first one.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 making video
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
This time we'll be focusing on the solo and shuffle units from the festival.
Let's take a look!
~~
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
~~~~
~~~
~~ Yes
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Yes, sir.
Music selection...
Like this.
Other than that...
Various.
Songs by our predecessors...
As candidates...
I had a hard time deciding.
But this song
This song...
the audition that led me to join Hello
Well...
I mean, solo...
I mean...
It was like a personal screening.
I performed that song
That song
"Only You".
The song "Only You" was
is a song that we sing together
isn't it?
You know...
The two main performers are there.
I mean, it's kind of like that.
In fact, at the time of the audition
I don't know if I was able to sing it.
I don't know if I was able to sing
I don't know.
It's a pretty distant memory.
But...
I sang in that size
I sang with a half
I can do it.
I mean...
I mean, I can do it.
I want to do it.
I want to do it right.
I want to do it in that size.
I wanted to do it in that size.
It doesn't happen very often.
I can't believe Mr. Mornin' did the song.
It was a great choice.
"Only You."
~She's a very nice lady.
And then
"Yo Yo Yo" and then they came out.
And then the two of them went back
Outside.
Let's do this.
~♪
If I tell you, you won't understand a word I'm saying.
This girl over here is the only one who's kamusharia
This girl over here is sexy
~~
I, Kitahara, was the first one to win.
It was my third time.
I've always wanted to win.
This time I used a little hand power
This time, I used my hand power to draw the winning ticket.
I was so happy to win!
I'm so happy that I won!
Last time I was in a trio with Janamin and Ms. Yajima
This time I was in a trio with Moe Kitahara and Kaumu.
Kaumu and I share the same birthday, so we talk a lot.
I talk with Kaumu a lot, but I haven't worked with Moe Kitahara that much.
I was so happy.
Before the raffle, I, Kawamura, was given a gift of gummy bears by Momo-chan.
Momo-chan had just given us some gummy bears as a present.
I said thank you and ate them.
Before that, Kikuta-san asked me how I liked the raffle.
We had a conversation about how the raffle hadn't been held yet.
I was talking to them that day, before the raffle.
I was talking to them that day, before the raffle, when I saw the person who won the raffle. It was like that.
I thought they were the ones I talked about earlier.
I felt like it was fate.
I love this trio so much.
So Moe Kitahara wrote their names in big letters.
I thought, "What's this?
And Kaumu wrote his name in big letters, too.
I thought, "This is the guy I have to match.
I was so happy!
When I saw that you two made the letters big together
I was so happy to see that you are the best senpai!
Next episode's preview
Pei couldn't make it, so I'll be doing it instead.
I have many feelings about it, but I think there are people who came to see Pei, and of course I have feelings for Pei.
I'm nervous, but I'm very grateful for the opportunity.
I think it's a great opportunity, so I'm going to do my best.
I'm so nervous. I don't know what to do. The stage is so different from usual.
The stage is different from usual, it's kind of square and everyone is surrounded.
I'm so nervous just going on the regular stage.
I'm so nervous about going on stage, but I'm going to do my best.
I will do my best.
me
Don't be nervous, believe in yourself, and believe in everyone who has come to see you,
I will do my best, thinking of FE.
Of course I'm very nervous, but I'm looking forward to it.
I have been wanting to win the shuffle for a long time, and I have been saving up my luck for a long time, so this is the third time I finally won,
I will treasure this precious opportunity and do my best so that everyone will be able to find me.
I have to be nervous when I am in a live concert venue, with its echoes, and with an audience, but I am determined to do my best.
But I am filled with the feeling of "I'm going to do something, I'm going to do my best.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching.
Here we go again
Come come
Yo yo yo
Come come come
Here we go again
Yes, well, my motto was "Let's do it with an open mind,
Well, when I was able to get up on stage, I thought, "Oh, I'm living on my own,
I saw the video later, really just now, just now I saw the video,
I was really nervous, which was a little frustrating, but I did my best.
I was a little frustrated, but I did my best. I think I was more relaxed than I thought I would be.
After I entered the venue, I watched the video and thought I wanted to rewatch it one more time,
I think the members and the performance were great.
It was so much fun. It was a scene I will never forget.
I burned it into my eyes.
The song is a little cool and sexy.
It's a sexy, mature song,
But the penlights, the penlights that the audience was holding...,
I was a little bit smitten when I saw the faces of the audience.
And there were times when I thought, "Oh, no, no, I have to be cool,
That's how amazing the power of the fans was to me.
I also had the chance to perform with Ikuta-san,
I felt like I had a good feeling during the rehearsal,
I felt like, you know, I was touching Ikuta-san, like this,
But when it came to the actual performance, we seemed to be more in sync with each other,
It was a lot of fun.
Now that you have seen it, how did you like it?
Well, I think the shuffle units and solos were unique to this Hina Fest,
Each group had a mix of all the group colors that they usually have through their activities,
On the other hand, I thought it was cool to see solo singers who were separated from their groups,
Kawana-san, who performed in place of Yuki Hirayama on short notice, was amazing,
I was also impressed by the quality of the performance, even though it was done on short notice, and I was impressed from the rehearsal,
I was so moved from the rehearsal that I was so moved that I was moved by what you were carrying.
I was so moved by Yuki's passion and the passion of the audience who came to see her performance.
Of course I was disappointed that Yuki Hirayama could not perform, but Rin Kawana, it's not like you didn't choose that song yourself.
That's right. Yuki Hirayama chose that song, and yet she sang it so well, so convincingly, that when I saw her singing it at the rehearsal, I thought it was really cool.
I saw her at the rehearsal, and I thought she was really cool.
I think the cheers from the fans on the day of the concert gave everyone a sense of accomplishment, and I am always grateful for their support. Thank you very much.
You also met Yumi, didn't you?
Yes, we did.
So please look forward to the release of the making of the film.
Yes, please do.
This is the making of Hello Project Kinafes 2024.
Raise it, the temperature at dawn, my song begins.
Watch me, closer, and go with me.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Next, here it is!
Ruri Hiromoto, Sumire Tashiro, Dance Lecture
In this corner, Ruri Hiromoto and Sumire Tashiro will give you a lecture on the choreography for the choruses of songs other than the singles!
Let's have a look!
This is Ruri Hiromoto and Sumire Tashiro from Ochanomama. In this corner, we're going to give you a lecture on the choreography of songs other than single songs.
Okay, what song are you going to lecture us about today?
Today's topic is...
Hello, there must be a reason why you were born. Sumire, please introduce this song.
Yes, this song has a very cute choreography, and it's also a song that we get really excited when we perform it live.
We will teach you how to dance to this song, so I hope you will learn it with us.
Thank you very much for watching!
Fluttering Carette
Yeah!
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Woo!
Now then, I'd like to start the lecture.
Rhythm of the chorus
Myself.
There's a "ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta" sound.
Tattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattattah.
I'll give you one left diagonal and one right hand.
Yes, sir.
Yo!
When I say "Yes, yes"...
Yes, sir.
Front foot, right foot, hello, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, and then the right hand.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Then, with your right hand... during the seven times... slowly rotate your right hand in a circular motion.
Now, from the right foot, right-left, right-right... and this right hand, which was directly above you... move it out at a slight angle, right-left, right-left, right-left.
Four times. And once more from the head.
Hello, 234567. Right, left, right, left, right, left.
Now that we're there, let's move on to the next one.
And then keep your index finger on it.
One, what's this one called? Write once on the side, then go down.
Halfway down the square. Halfway down. Here we go.
Seven times.
I'll look at it...
One, two, three, four, five, six.
In the middle, yes.
Step on the right foot, step on the left foot, and then stab forward.
Okay, then...
Sokie, let's start with "Ito"... "Sokie Ito", "Ito", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "middles", "stabbing"...
Okay, one more time from the head. - Yes, one sherry.
Rock, paper, scissors! Hello! Hello!
One, two, three, four, five, six, center, turn, turn, stab, perfect, yes.
And now we move on to the next one, hands together.
Hands, bottom, above the head, above that, straight up, four times, gradually, shoulders, head, above that, straight up, four times.
For the feet, we'll do "choo-chong, choo-chong, choo-chong, choo-chong" four times.
Hands and feet together.
Then jump to the left and turn around, while keeping your hands free
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, yes.
Then, after your right hand is ready, run 1, 2, 3, 4, 4 times as if you were running.
Ready?
Yes, one, two, three, four.
One more time. This part is a little bit difficult, so let's do "se-no", shoulder, head, up, straight, wait, tatta, yes, 1, 2, 3, 4...
Here, the head and face are also straight, and the hand is over here.
At an angle. Yes, yes, yes. Then, look forward here, and run, rattling, rattling, rattling.
That's right. Yes. Yes. Next? Shall we go? Let's go. Yes, let's go. And then,
1, 2, 3, 4, and then 1, 2, 3, 4, and then 1, 2 again with your right hand,
Turn,
Turn, and then stab.
Stab.
Yes, what do you want to stab?
Stab the sun or the sky.
Aim at the sky with this.
Aim at the sky.
Then, make it a par, and spin it around and around with a sparkle.
The par version of the previous one.
Yes, turn it all the way around,
Yay, yay, yay with a super happy smile.
Yay, happy.
Happy smile.
And then, open your arms out, starting from the right,
Then put them back in position, legs closed,
From the left,
Yay.
Yes.
Now, please enjoy your impressions.
Enjoy.
So, where shall we start?
Let's start from here.
Yes, let's start here.
Let's go.
Ready?
What's up, Jan?
It won't happen,
Even if you fall down,
One, two, three, four,
Turn, turn, turn,
Zos.
Sparkle.
Yay.
Both hands.
Even at this time,
I love you~.
Seino.
Woo-hoo-hoo.
Yay.
Oh~.
So that's how it is.
What do you think?
How's it going? Is it done?
I heard it's done.
It's great.
It's great, guys.
You're learning very quickly.
Okay, I'll start from the beginning again.
Here we go.
Let's start from the beginning.
Hello 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7,
Right, left,
One, two, three, four, five, six,
Middle,
Turn, turn,
Jan.
Sean.
Shoulder, head,
Up,
Straight,
Rumble,
Jajan.
One, two, three, four,
Turn, turn, turn,
Zos.
Sparkle.
Yay.
Anytime.
I love you.
Seino
Yay!
That's great.
Anyway...
Let's get into the groove and put on a happy smile
Let's have fun!
Can we do it?
Yay!
So let's start with the song!
~~
Thank you for watching!
Well, that's the end of the dance lecture.
How was everyone?
How was it?
Perfect!
Wonderful!
I hope you enjoy this song with a smile and a happy heart.
Yes, this song is really about having fun.
So please dance with the spirit of enjoyment in your hearts.
That's all for now, this is the dance lecture of "Hello, There Must Be a Meaning to Your Birth"!
This is Lily Hiromoto and Sumire Tashiro from Ocha-no-Mano
and Sumire Tashiro.
Bye bye!
Yes, I was dancing to this song with four of my classmates when Ochanono-san was performing it.
But I didn't really know the proper choreography, so I was given a dance lecture like this.
I wanted to spread the choreography to my classmates so that we could all learn it together and perfect it.
It's nice, it's cute, and it looks good on you.
Really?
I love it here.
This way.
It's a little different.
Look again.
Yes, please.
We Morning Musume。 We Morning Musume did this song at the New Year's concert in 2023.
I wish I could have seen this song earlier.
At that time, we did the choreography by ourselves.
So this video really makes the Hello Project members happy.
Yes, the Hello Project members are happy too.
Even more so.
Yes.
And so are the fans.
That's right.
I'm sure they'll be able to dance with us.
It would be really cute if everyone danced together.
So cute!
It's a song that's going to be a lot of fun.
Yes, it is.
That's all for now.
This was a dance lecture by Ruri Hiromoto and Sumire Tashiro.
Let's work hard together!
This message is brought to you by Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 24 and Ayumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
and Ayumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
Next, here we go!
Tsubaki Factory Stay Free & Stay Tune Chorus Recording
From Tsubaki Factory's latest album
Stay Free & Stay Tune chorus recording
Well, I need to be more aggressive.
I want to load up a little bit of
That diddy diddy diddy
Wait, can I at least get a head start?
I need to be more aggressive.
I'm going to go.
I'm gonna have to go harder.
That looks good.
Can I do it at my car?
Sure.
Let's go for it.
Yes, sir.
Let's do more!
Let's attack more!
Yes, sir.
Let's do the last one.
Can we do the regular one?
We have to go harder.
Let's go for it.
Let's get aggressive.
Music
Let's get more aggressive.
Doubles
Let's get more aggressive, let's get more aggressive
Shall we go upstairs?
Yes, sir.
Fast forward.
Let's get more aggressive.
Let's get to the bottom of this.
Here... and here.
Let me see the bottom.
We've got to keep pushing... and pushing... and pushing.
Let's go all the way.
I guess so.
I agree.
More.
Let's go further.
Let's go to the end of the rust. - Yeah. Can we go with a whoosh? Okay, yes.
Stay free. I don't think we should be satisfied.
Stay tuned
Embracing the things that mustn't change
Stay free
I feel like I shouldn't be satisfied
You think it's good
Stay free
I feel like I shouldn't be satisfied
Yes, I do.
Stayfree
I feel like I shouldn't be satisfied
Let's go out and stay tuned
Embracing what must not be changed
Perfect!
Let's give this one a listen, shall we?
Yes, yes, I do.
Stay Free
I don't think we should be satisfied.
Go, go, stay tuned!
Embrace the things you mustn't change
Yes, sir.
It's good.
It's really good.
Yeah.
Let's see,
This is what a massage feels like.
So,
STAY!
WOHOHOHOHOHOHO...
Everyone will care if you do it.
WOHOHOHOHOHO...
wohohohohoho...
Ah~
cheap as a customer's street
amos
У on
~~
Can I just do the first group?
Yes У on
~~
You don't want some hamo?
Put it down, pikey.
Yeah, put it down.
~~
Okay, let's go.
Here we go.
~~
~♪
By the way, I'll sing over this first.
If you hang in there
I'll go for another one.
~♪
I can hear you, though.
Indeed.
So why not have the middle be the main battleground?
If you want them to hear you, it's better to put the top one in.
I see.
~I see...
Stayfree, I don't think we should be satisfied.
It's a world I haven't seen yet.
When I left APRONT, I left a lot of demos behind.
He listened to them and dug them out of the stock.
I'd forgotten that I'd even written the song.
The prototype.
I had to rearrange it to make it more punkish and modern.
And it had to be modern.
I had to make it 2024.
I had to rework the lyrics and the arrangement one more time to make it perfect.
It's a surf rock song, if you want to call it a genre.
In terms of genre, it's a song called "Surf Rock".
If I had one request, it would be
If I could make one request, it would be for the last part of the song
The part at the end of the song where it says "war war war war war"...
It's completely in a male key.
That part at the end...
I don't want you to sing the lyrics.
If you focus on the "war-war-war-war" at the end of the song
I think it will make the live more exciting.
I'd appreciate it if you could do that.
Ska-punk surf rock really fits the bill!
It's a great rock 'n' roll punkish song.
It's a rollicking punkish song.
Please check out Stay Free's
It's not stayfree.
Please check out the lyrics written by Takeshi Nakajima
Tsubaki Factory's
Stay Free & Stay Tune
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I've given you a look at the recording of the chorus.
This song is a song that we can really get excited about with our fans.
When we first came to Tsubaki Factory
I had an image of Tsubaki Factory being sad and fragile.
but as Takuya Nakajima said earlier
It has a rocky feel to it.
The other day at the 7th anniversary live Realize
I sang with a live band
Takuya Nakajima's music is very detailed.
Takuya Nakajima's music is also very detailed.
I was so excited to sing this song with a live band.
I wanted to get excited about this song even more.
As for my favorite part of the song
When Mr. Miyanokizora sang "Come on everybody!
Come on everybody!
I thought it was really unusual for Miyano-san to do that.
I thought it was really unusual.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I think it's pretty close to the first time.
That's the best part of the song.
The audience can really get excited with this song.
As Takuya-san said earlier in the call
In the chorus
"Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
There's a place in the recording
There's a place where we recorded the chorus
I'd like to sing that part together with everyone.
I'd like to sing the intro and the outro.
I'd like to sing the intro and outro together.
The choreography is like punching the person next to you for the third time, or punching the audience.
The choreography is like punching the person next to you for the third time, or punching the audience for the third time.
The dancing, singing, and calls are all very exciting.
It's a song that you can get really excited about.
I hope you will watch the chorus video at the concert and call out the chorus.
I would like you to watch the chorus video at the concert and call out to the chorus.
Takuya-san really vocalizes without hesitation.
That's why he's so powerful.
I was reminded of that by this video of the chorus recording.
I really like this song!
It looks great live!
Thank you very much!
I'm very happy.
I felt that this is a song that the members and fans
I felt that this song should be nurtured by the members and fans together.
I'm looking forward to seeing it live!
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
Tsubaki Factory
Stay Free & Stay Tuned!
Coding
Don't let it be tears, don't let it be tomorrow, even though you're already someone else's person
I can't erase the smile that's embedded in your heart, I want to erase it, but I can't
Don't worry! It's going to be alright!
It's time for Yumi Ishida and Yumi Kasai to say goodbye to UPKAMI!
We've seen a lot of different images this time.
I, Kasai, was really impressed with Takuya Nakajima's Stay Free & Stay Tune chorus video.
It was so cool!
It was really cool and I could get excited with the audience.
I would like you to watch the video and practice the chorus.
I would like you to watch the video and practice the chorus with the audience.
As for me...
Hello, there must be a reason why I was born.
Dance lecture video
The way the two of them are dancing in the video...
It's because the choreography is so simple
That's why it's so interesting to see their individuality.
I actually thought it was interesting.
Sumire Tashiro is a little bit like this.
I thought the way Sumire Tashiro put her shoulders and hips into the video was really good, and I thought that's the kind of song it was.
In this show, we'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group, so please subscribe to our channel and we'll be bringing you the parts you don't normally see.
This time, we'll be talking with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume 24 and Yuumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami, we will be talking with Manabana Inaba Pink Temperture, making of a music video shoot, and Hello!
and the making of the music video shoot. Project Kinafession 2024.
Please look forward to it!
~~
More than red, more amazing than red, roque erotica
More cozy than a dream